https://info.ucfactors.com/en-us/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
800-228-7151
Client Login
Contact Us
What is Factoring?
Privacy Policy
What information do we collect?We collect information from you when you register on our site, subscribe to our newsletter or fill out a form. When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address or phone number. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.What do we use your information for?Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:To personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)To improve our website (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)To improve customer service (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site featureTo send periodic emailsNote: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, please email us info@ucfactors.com.How do we protect your information?We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information.Do we use cookies?Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. We use cookies to compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.RemarketingWe also may use cookies to serve ads based upon a user’s prior visit to our website using Google Remarketing. This allows third party vendors including Google to show advertisements of our products and services on the internet. You may opt out of Google’s use of cookies by visiting Google’s advertising opt out page at : http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/ads/Do we disclose any information to outside parties?We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.Third party links.Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.Online Privacy Policy OnlyThis online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.Terms and ConditionsPlease also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at www.ucfactors.comYour ConsentBy using our site, you consent to our online privacy policy.Changes to our Privacy PolicyIf we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.Last updated: 2011.11.28
2200 East Route 66, Unit 102
Glendora, CA, 91740
(909) 394-5400
info@ucfactors.com
What is Factoring?
